sendgb.com 2019-07-15

# Sendgb.com | Privacy Policy

For SendGB, the privacy of personal information is essential. Data can be collected at any time while using our products and services. The collected data is only used by SendGB to help improve the site / service and is not shared with third parties. 

The SendGB site takes precautions to prevent unauthorized access to the information of the person. The information belonging to our users is only given to third parties or institutions by court decision. User information (behavior) can be used by SendGB to provide better service. 

**Collected data pertaining to the user during the use of SendGB;**

Uploaded file type,  
File size,  
Number of files,  
Receivers Email addresses,  
Sender email address,  
Sender's IP address, browser information, location information,  
The recipient's IP address, browser information, location information,

**SendGB** will not receive credit card or payment information from users. 

**SendGB** uses the SSL-Secure Sockets Layer (secure login layer) certificate for security between users and servers. 

**SendGB** uses **"Cookies"** like many websites. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. 

For example, **SendGB** loads a cookie that remembers your user ID to make your next visit easier. 

**SendGB** is so important to your personal information security that it handles very little personal data. You do not need to register to use **SendGB**. We do not have an entry procedure for our free services. 

To use our service and send your files, you may need to enter your own e-mail address, the files (recipients) you want to send and the e-mail addresses of the recipients. With your file you can also add a personal message for recipients. **SendGB** must be able to process this data when sending files to ensure that you use our service. Basically we will use your personal data only to send your file and improve our services. Of course, we will not sell it to third parties or affiliated parties or use it for disturbing commercial messages. 

If you have any questions about how **SendGB** handles your personal data, please send an email to [info@sendgb.com](mailto:info@sendgb.com) to **SendGB**. 

You can always safely use **SendGB.com** for large file sending.
